《暮光之城4：破晓（下）》
你太美了
So beautiful.
现在我们有着同样的体温
We're the same temperature now.
嘿 贝拉
Hey, Bella,
你现在比我更为强壮
you're a lot stronger than I am right now.
你可不要把我给揉碎了
It's your turn not to break me.
我爱你
I love you.
蕾妮斯梅呢
Renesmee.
她很了不起
She's incredible.
她在哪里? 我要去看看她
Where is she? I have to see her.
先等一等
Wait. Wait.
你必须先控制好自己对血的渴求
You need to get your thirst under control.
而且你还得去猎食
Yeah, you'll need to hunt.
闭上你的眼睛
Close your eyes.
你听到什么?
What do you hear?
贝拉 不要!
Bella, don't!
贝拉 停下来!
Bella, stop!
对不起 我没想到在这荒山野岭里 还会有人
I'm sorry, I didn't realize there'd be people this far from the trails.
我得离开这里
I have to get outta here.
好的 我可以帮你
Okay, I can help you.
或者不用我帮
Or not.
这真让我惊叹
Well, I'm amazed.
你能够在猎食人血的途中抽身离去
You ran away from human blood mid-hunt.
即使是成熟的吸血鬼 还无法做到这点
Even mature vampires have problems with that.
你还在这里
You're still here.
你也是
So are you.
我没有想到你还是那么地
I didn't expect you to seem so
一如既往
you.
除了这诡异的瞳孔
Except for the creepy eyes.
我会保持距离的
I would keep my distance for now.
为了宝宝的安全 得先看一下你是如何与我相处的
It's safer for the baby to see how you do with me first.
你啥时候开始在乎蕾妮斯梅了?
Since when do you care about Renesmee?
好的
All right.
吸一口气
Take a whiff.
好吧 我现在明白大家讨论的是什么了
Well, I can see what everyone's been talking about.
雅各布 你身上确实有股臭味
Jake, you really do stink.
你们俩
You guys
看上去真的很般配
really look great together.
你想过来看看我们的女儿吗?
Want to come meet our daughter?
欢迎回家
Welcome to the family.
贝拉 你看上去精神翊翊
You look amazing, Bella.
有人在这里等着见你呢
Someone's been waiting to meet you.
露丝 你好
Rose.
你真美
Beautiful.
那是什么?
What was that?
她向你展示了她对你的最初记忆
She showed you the first memory she has of you.
向我展示? 怎么做到的?
Showed me? How?
就像是我是如何能读到别人的想法?
How do I hear thoughts?
爱丽丝是如何能够预见未来的呢?
How does Alice see the future?
她天赋异禀
She's gifted.
我真的只离开了两天吗?
I've only been out for two days?
她的生长速度 相当之快
Her growth rate is unprecedented.
好了 今天就先到此为止吧
All right. That's enough experimenting for one day.
雅各布 别这样
Jacob.
她适应得很好
She's doing great.
是的 但我们也不要逼得太紧
Yeah. Let's not push it though.
你是怎么一回事啊?
What's your problem?
噢
Oh.
告诉她吧 雅各布
Do tell her, Jacob.
没问题的
This should be good.
先等一等
Hold on a second.
贝拉 你听我说
Bella.
是这样的
Look,
就是狼人的事
it's a wolf thing.
什么狼人的事?
What's a wolf thing?
呃...
Um...
你知道这是我们无法控制的
You know we have no control over it.
我们也无法选择发生的对象
We can't choose who it happens with.
而且事情不是你想的那样 贝拉 我发誓
And it doesn't mean what you think, Bella. I promise.
先把蕾妮斯梅带出去
Take Renesmee out of the room.
噢
Oh.
爱德华 现在不要碰我
Edward, don't touch me right now.
我不想伤到你
I don't want to hurt you.
噢
Oh.
你居然给我女儿打下狼族印记?
You imprinted on my daughter?
我是逼不得已!
It wasn't my choice!
她只是个婴儿!
She's a baby!
事情不是这样的
It's not like that.
如果真是这样 你觉得爱德华会饶了我吗?
You think Edward would let me live if it was?
我现在仍半信半疑
I'm still debating it.
我只抱过她一次!
I've held her once!
就一次 雅各布!
One time, Jacob!
而你就认为自己可以对她宣示
And already you think that you have some moronic
所谓的狼人所有权了?
wolfy claim on her?
这是我的女儿!
She's mine!
没关系 莉亚
It's fine, Leah.
你必须离她远远的
You're gonna stay away from her.
你知道这点我无法做到
You know I can't do that.
爱德华 拦住她
Stop her, Edward.
他说了没关系啊
He said it's fine.
她很了不起 对吧?
She's amazing, right?
你还记得自己在三天前 是有多希望我能陪在你身边吗?
Do you remember how much you wanted to be around me 3 days ago?
此情不在了 是吧?
That's gone now, right?
早就消逝了
Long gone.
因为其实是她需要我
Because it was her.
从一开始 希望我能在场的就是尼斯
From the beginning it was Nessie who wanted me there.
什么 尼斯?
Nessie?
你还给我女儿取了个外号 叫尼斯湖怪物?
You nicknamed my daughter after the Loch Ness monster?
塞斯 你没事吧?
Seth, are you okay?
塞斯 对不起
Seth, I'm sorry.
他会没事的
He'll be all right.
贝拉
Bella,
你比任何人都更了解我
you know me better than anyone.
我只是想要小尼斯...
All I want is for Ness...
蕾妮斯梅能够安全幸福地成长
Renesmee to be safe. Happy.
你想想
Look,
从前的那些事情 让人百思不解
nothing ever made sense before.
你 我 以及这一切
You. Me. Any of it.
而现在我知道原因了
And now I understand why.
原因在于她
This was the reason.
终于都来了
Finally.
轮到我了
My turn.
她睡在哪里?
Where does she sleep?
睡在我怀里 或是爱德华和爱斯梅的怀里
In my arms. Or Edward's or Esme's.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
我从三天前开始 年纪就不再长了
I stopped aging three days ago.
反正我们就是要庆祝 所以你就忍着吧
Well, we're celebrating anyway. So suck it up.
我还是讨厌惊喜 这一点并没有变
I still hate surprises. That hasn't changed.
你会喜欢这个惊喜的
You'll love this one.
欢迎到家!
Welcome home!
我们想着 你们俩应该想要一个自己的小窝
We thought you guys might like a place of your own.
你觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
我觉得非常棒
I think it's perfect.
进去瞧瞧
Go inside.
祝你们愉快
Have fun.
这里是蕾妮斯梅的房间
This will be Renesmee's room.
衣柜
Closet.
哇
Wow.
是爱丽丝为你购置的
Alice stocked it for you.
显而易见
Clearly.
这是我们的卧室
This is our room.
吸血鬼不睡觉的
Vampires don't sleep.
这不是用来睡觉的
It's not intended for sleep.
你之前确实在克制着自己
You really were holding back before.
我肯定会要不够你的
I'm never gonna get enough of this.
反正我们不会累
We don't get tired.
我们不用休息 不用喘气 还不用吃东西
We don't have to rest or catch our breath or eat.
我是说
I mean,
我们怎么停得下来啊?
how are we gonna stop?
罗莎莉和埃米特就很缠绵 足足十年了
Rosalie and Emmett were so bad, it took a solid decade
我们才能受得了站在他们身旁
before we could stand to be within five miles of them.
我觉得我们会更缠绵
I think we might be worse.
绝对会
Definitely worse.
哟
Wow.
做完了?
Done already?
蕾妮斯梅在哪里?
Where's Renesmee?
被那个金发妞偷走了
Blondie stole her.
你们弄坏了不少的东西吧?
Break a lot of stuff?
埃米特
Emmett.
别这样
No.
是查理打来的吗?
Is that Charlie?
他每天都来电两次
He's been calling twice a day.
他现在很憔悴
He's in pretty rough shape.
但我们最终还是得告诉他 你没有活过来
Eventually, we'll have to tell him you didn't make it.
只能让他哀痛 贝拉
He needs to mourn, Bella.
好吧 我们明天再告诉他
Okay. We'll do it tomorrow.
我会想念这里的
I'm gonna miss this place.
我们会回来的 向来都如此
We'll come back. We always do.
等一下
Wait.
没有人说过离开一事啊
Nobody said anything about leaving.
当大家都相信贝拉病逝了 我们就不能让她曝光
Once people believe Bella's dead, we can't risk anyone seeing her.
所以你们就这样消失?
So you just disappear?
雅各布 我们也是迫不得已
Jacob, we don't have another choice.
嘿
Hey.
你有听到什么消息吗?
You heard anything?
查理
Charlie,
贝拉她...
Bella is...
呃...
Uh...
不 她没死
No, she's not.
不不不 我是说 她挺好的
No, no, no, I mean, she's fine.
她回到家了
She's back home and
而且状态好多了
she's feeling better.
那你刚才怎么不说? 这就好
Why didn't you say so? That's great.
等一下
Wait.
有件事情你必须先了解
There's something you need to see first.
我要去见贝拉
I need to see Bella.
听着
Look,
为了让贝拉好转 她必须
in order for Bella to get better, she had to
转化
change.
"转化" 这是什么意思?
What do you mean, "change"?
别误解我
Here goes nothing.
你这是要干什么?
What the hell are you doing?
你所处的世界 其实并不是你想的那样
You don't live in the world you think you do.
雅各布 快把衣服穿上
Jacob, put your clothes on.
这也许看上去很奇怪
Now, this may seem strange.
真的很奇怪 但是
Really strange. But
每天都有更奇怪的事情发生
stranger things happen every day.
相信我
Trust me.
天啊!
Holy shit!
我把问题解决了
Look, I solved a problem.
你们却要离开
You were leaving.
你还要我怎么办?
What did you expect me to do?
你根本没有意识到 你让他陷入险境之中
You don't realize the danger you've put him in.
沃尔图里家族会把发现我们身份的人类都杀掉
The Volturi will kill anyone who knows about us.
不 我没有把你的身份告诉他 我只说了我的
No, I didn't tell him about you. Just me.
我只说了你和别人不一样
I only said you were different.
还说我们还收养了一个侄女
And that we have a niece who we adopted.
说真的 雅各布 他肯定还会继续追问的
I mean, seriously, Jake, he's not just gonna let that go.
你考虑过他会给贝拉带来多大的痛苦吗?
Did you consider the physical pain he'll put Bella through?
这就像是把热烙铁直接插她的喉咙里
It'll be like sticking a white hot branding iron down her throat.
正如她要竭力控制自己对血的欲望那样
And that's assuming she can control her thirst.
查理现在非常痛苦
Look, Charlie's been in hell.
我知道 有他在你的生活里 你会过得更幸福
And I know you'll be much happier with him in your life.
雅各布 你别装得好像是为别人好 其实你是为了自己
Jacob, don't try and pretend you're doing this for anyone but yourself.
抱歉 会让你有这种看法
Sorry you feel that way
因为他十分钟后就到这里了
because he'll be here in 10 minutes.
什么?
What?
你的眼睛刚开始会有点不适
These will irritate your eyes at first.
关键在于不要移动得太快
The main thing is not to move too fast.
试着去那边坐下 双腿交叉
Try taking a seat. Crossing your legs.
也许还应该再慢一点 嗯
Maybe a tad slower. Hmm.
每分钟最起码眨眼三次
And blink at least three times a minute.
很好
Good.
卡通人物才这样吧
For a cartoon character.
屏住呼吸 有助于控制对血的渴求
Hold your breath. It will help with the thirst.
但是要记住耸肩 这会让你看上去就像是在呼吸
Just don't forget to move your shoulders so it looks like you're breathing.
还有 别坐得太直
And don't sit so straight.
人类的坐姿不是这样的
Humans don't do that.
好的 我掌握住了
Okay. I got it.
走动 眨眼 耷拉着身子
Move around, blink, slouch.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你好 查理
Hello, Charlie.
贝拉在哪里
Where's Bella?
贝拉
Bella.
爸 你好
Hi, Dad.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
好极了
Never better.
壮如小马
Healthy as a horse.
你该不会也能变身成为动物吧?
You don't turn into an animal, too, do you?
她倒是想有那么厉害
She wishes she was that awesome.
让他们单独聊聊吧
Let's give them some privacy.
雅各布说这是...
Uh, Jake said that this...
这是必需的
This was necessary.
这话是什么意思?
What does that mean?
我真的觉得 你还是...
I really think it would be better...
我想知道你出了什么事
I wanna know what happened to you.
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
你应该给我个解释
I think I deserve an explanation.
确实
You do.
但如果你真要知道 那我就不能留在这里了
But if you really need one, I can't stay here.
拜托! 别这样!
Oh, come on! No!
不要再离开了!
No more going away!
爸 你只需相信 不管怎样
Dad, you're just gonna have to trust that for whatever reason,
我确实很好
I'm all right.
我现在好极了
I'm more than all right.
你能接受这个说法吗?
Can you live with that?
我能否接受这个说法?
Can I live with that?
我不知道 贝拉
Well, I don't know, Bella.
我亲眼目睹了 一个自己从小看到大的孩子
I mean, I just watched a kid I've known his entire life
变身成为大狼狗
turn into a very large dog.
而我的女儿 看上去像是我女儿
My daughter looks like my daughter.
但其实不然
But doesn't.
你可以相信我吗 我会把你需要知道的事情都告诉你
Can you please just believe that I'll tell you anything that you need to know?
而这事是我不需要知道的?
And I don't need to know this?
是的
No.
真的 你不用知道
Really, you don't.
好吧...
Well...
我不想再失去你
Not gonna lose you again.
我承受不起
I can't.
你不会的
Then you won't.
我保证
I promise.
我想你 贝拉
I missed you, Bells.
很想你
So much.
爸 我也想你
I missed you, Dad.
查理
Charlie.
这个是蕾妮斯梅
This is Renesmee.
你的侄女?
Your niece?
是我们的女儿
Our daughter.
没错了
Right.
收养的
The adoption.
叫蕾妮斯梅?
Renee-semee?
她遗传了你的眼睛 贝拉
She's got your eyes, Bella.
我想 这是我需要知道的
Need to know, I guess.
做得好 贝拉
Well done, Bella.
从未见过新生吸血鬼 能有这般自制力的
Never seen a newborn show that kind of restraint.
我都不确定她是不是新生吸血鬼
I'm not sure she is a newborn.
她现在如此乏味
She's so tame.
埃米特 你不要惹她
Emmett, don't antagonize her.
她是全屋子里最强大的一个
She's the strongest one in the house.
请
Please.
埃米特 不要弄伤自己哟
Don't hurt yourself, Emmett.
好的 数到三开始
All right. On 3.
一
1,
二
2,
三!
3!
看到了吗?
Did you see that?
谢谢
Thank you.
我作为人类的时光已经结束
My time as a human was over.
但我却觉得现在更有活力
But I never felt more alive.
我生来就适合成为吸血鬼
I was born to be a vampire.
一切皆尘埃落定
Everything was falling into place.
就连沃尔图里家族 似乎也接受了我的新身份
Even the Volturi seemed to accept my new status.
尽管他们最终仍需证明
Though they'd want proof eventually.
现在 我们似乎仅存一个敌人
It seemed we had only one enemy left.
时间
Time.
蕾妮斯梅长得太快了
Renesmee was growing too fast.
我们都担心还能与她相处多久
We all worried about how long we would have with her.
这使得每一分每一秒 都倍感珍贵
It just made every moment more precious.
看 是雪花
Look, a snowflake.
这真美
It's beautiful.
你不如再去接一朵?
Why don't you go get another one?
爱德华认为我们能在巴西找到这些事情的答案
Edward thinks that we'll find answers in Brazil.
那里有些部落 或许对此有所了解
There are tribes there that might know something.
那人是谁?
Who was that?
她应该是我们在德纳里的堂亲
I think that's our cousin from Denali.
伊丽娜!
Irina!
塔尼娅说服伊丽娜来与我们和解
Tanya convinced Irina to come reconcile with us.
但她似乎改变了主意
It looks like she changed her mind.
看到雅各布也在 她肯定觉得难以接受
Seeing Jacob must have been too much for her.
真希望我能跟她谈一谈
Wish I could have just spoken to her.
她是亲戚 会适应过来的
She's family. She'll come around.
真让人喜出望外
What a pleasant surprise.
你要怎么样?
What do you want?
嗯?
Hmm?
我是来举报一项罪行的
I have to report a crime.
柯伦一家...
The Cullens...
他们做了一些可怕的事情
They've done something terrible.
请允许我 亲爱的
Allow me, my dear.
天啊
Oh, my.
怎么了 爱丽丝?
What is it, Alice?
沃尔图里家族
The Volturi.
他们正冲着我们而来
They're coming for us.
有阿罗 凯厄斯 马库斯 护卫队
Aro, Caius, Marcus, the Guard.
以及伊丽娜
And Irina.
亲爱的 过来
Honey, come here.
为什么?
Why?
伊丽娜在林子里看到什么?
What did Irina see in the woods?
我们当时只是在散步
We were just walking.
小尼斯则与雪花嬉戏
Ness was catching snowflakes.
那就难怪了
Of course.
伊丽娜认为蕾妮斯梅是吸血鬼幼童
Irina thinks Renesmee's an Immortal Child.
吸血鬼幼童都长得很俊俏
The Immortal Children were very beautiful.
极其迷人
So enchanting.
只要接近他们 就会爱上他们
To be near them was to love them.
但是当他们变成吸血鬼 便会停止生长
But their development was frozen at the age they were turned.
他们无法被教导 或者被限制
They couldn't be taught or restrained.
随便发个脾气 便足以摧毁整个村庄
A single tantrum could destroy an entire village.
人类听说了这起毁灭性的事件
Humans heard about the devastation.
流言四起
Stories spread.
沃尔图里家族被迫插手其中
The Volturi were forced to intervene.
因为孩子们无法保守我们的秘密
Since the Children couldn't protect our secret,
那只能把他们处置了
they had to be destroyed.
不要!
No!
住手!
创造者对他们极其疼爱 并竭力保护
Their creators grew very attached and fought to protect them.
而长期以来建立的族系 就此被摧毁
Long-established covens were torn apart.
无数的人类 惨遭杀戮
Countless humans slaughtered.
传统 朋友
Traditions, friends,
甚至家人 皆凋敝零落
even families. Lost.
不要!
No, no!
- 妈妈!  - 不要!
- Mother!  - No!
妈妈!
Mother!
所以德纳里的妈妈 创造了一个吸血鬼幼童?
So the Denalis' mother made an Immortal Child?
是的
Yes.
她为此付出代价
And she paid the price.
蕾妮斯梅和这些孩子可不一样
Well, Renesmee's nothing like those children.
她生来如此 并不是被咬所致 而且她每天都在生长
She was born, not bitten. She grows every single day.
你不能向沃尔图里解释这种情况吗?
So can't you just explain that to the Volturi?
阿罗从伊丽娜的思维中 得到足够的证据
Aro has enough proof in Irina's thoughts.
那我们就抗争
So we fight.
他们的进攻武器过于强大
Their offensive weapons are too powerful.
谁都无法与简抗衡
No one can stand against Jane.
而亚历克更加厉害
Alec's even worse.
那我们就说服他们
Well, then we convince them.
他们是来杀我们 而不是来谈话的
They're coming to kill us, not to talk.
是的 你说的对
No, you're right.
他们不会听我们的
They won't listen to us.
但也许其他人能够说服他们
But maybe others can convince them.
卡莱尔 你的朋友遍布全世界
Carlisle, you have friends all around the world.
我不能叫他们一起来抗争
I won't ask them to fight.
不必抗争 只需作证
Not fight. Witness.
如果有足够的人了解到真相
If enough people knew the truth,
也许我们可以说服沃尔图里家族听我们解释
maybe we could convince the Volturi to listen.
这一点 我们可以请求朋友们的帮忙
We can ask this of our friends.
至少我们又可以去伦敦了
At least we get to go to London again.
我们已经很久没有去那里了
We haven't been there in a long time.
好了 我们赶紧上路吧
All right. Let's get this show on the road.
爱丽丝叫我把这个给你
Alice asked me to give you that.
她和贾斯珀昨晚闯进我们的领地 往海那边去了
She and Jasper crossed our lands to the ocean last night.
卡莱尔 怎么了?
Carlisle?
他们离开了我们
They've left us.
为什么?
Why?
她没有说
She didn't say.
能让我看看吗?
Can I see that?
在开始积雪之前 尽可能地多召集证人
Gather as many witnesses as you can before the snow sticks to the ground.
他们会在那个时候到来
That's when they'll come.
(《威尼斯商人》  威廉·莎士比亚)
爱丽丝的指示很清楚 但仍存疑问
Alice's instructions were clear, but the question remained.
为什么在我们最需要他们的时候 她和贾斯珀却离开了?
Why would she and Jasper leave at the moment we needed them most?
他们知道些什么?
What did they know?
我们一路向北 去拜访我们的近亲 以此开启了寻求证人之旅
Our search for witnesses began with a trip north to our closest relatives.
爱德华 一切可好?
Edward, is everything all right?
怎么不告诉我们 你们要来啊?
Why didn't you tell us you were coming?
是因为伊丽娜吗?
Is it Irina?
你们有她的消息吗?
Have you heard from her?
都是听别人说的
Not directly.
为什么你的新娘在车上等?
Why is your bride waiting in the car?
还有 为什么还带了头狼与你们同行?
And why have you brought a wolf with you?
我在这里就能闻到他的臭味
I can smell him from here.
我们家族身处险境 我需要你们的帮忙
My family is in danger. I need your help.
发生什么事了?
What's happened?
这实在难以解释
It's hard to explain
但我需要你能够摒除偏见 可以吗?
but I need you to be open-minded. Can you do that?
当然
Of course.
好的
Okay.
是时候去见一些新面孔
Time to meet some new people.
如果他们不喜欢我怎么办?
What if they don't like me?
- 他们会喜欢你的  - 他们会的
- They'll love you.  - They will.
只要他们了解你
Once they understand you.
他们只是从未见过像你这样的
They just haven't met anyone like you before.
好了
Okay.
沃尔图里会把我们都杀掉
The Volturi will come for all of us.
快把那东西带离这里
You get that thing out of here.
她的本质是不一样的
She's not what she looks like.
这可是一种罪行!
This is a crime!
退后!
Stay back!
她的血管里 有鲜血在流动
She has blood in her veins.
你可以感受到她的温度
You can feel her warmth.
我能感觉得到
I can feel it.
我是她的亲生父亲
I'm her biological father.
- 贝拉是她的母亲  - 不可能
- Bella is her mother.  - Impossible.
千真万确 她出生在我还是人类的时候
It's true. She was born while I was still human.
这真是闻所未闻
I've never heard of such a thing.
如果你愿意 她可以展示给你看
She can show you, if you let her.
塔尼娅 这是你欠我们的
Tanya, you owe us this much.
因为你的妹妹不让我们解释 而给我们招致杀身大祸
We're all under a death sentence because your sister didn't let us explain.
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
这是她沟通的方式
This is how she communicates.
这是真的
It's true.
她不是吸血鬼
She's not immortal.
我知道其他族人也会感到同样的畏惧
I knew the rest of our family would face this fear as well.
畏惧着未知
Fear of the unknown.
畏惧着沃尔图里家族
Fear of the Volturi.
阿蒙 求你了!
Amun, please!
卡莱尔 我帮不了你
I cannot help you, Carlisle.
如果不是事态紧急 我也不会求你
I wouldn't ask if it weren't urgent.
你必须走了
You must go.
我愿闻其详
I'd like to hear about it.
我从没见过阿蒙的朋友
I never get to meet any of Amun's friends.
他喜欢把我藏起来
He likes to keep me hidden.
我觉得没必要啊
I can't imagine why.
- 我是卡莱尔  - 我是本杰明
- Carlisle.  - Benjamin.
本杰明可以改变各种元素的形态
Benjamin can influence the elements.
而我拥有超凡的自控力
And here I get super self-control.
他们是谁?
Who are they?
是塞纳和扎弗里娜
Senna and Zafrina.
来自亚马逊
From the Amazon.
塞纳和扎弗里娜的到来 意味着即便是世上
The arrival of Senna and Zafrina meant that our plea was being heard
最偏远的角落 也听说了我们的诉求
in even the most remote corners of the world
而且其他人则在寻找邻近的证人
while others searched for witnesses closer to home.
卡莱尔与一名爱国者的初见 是在约克城的战场上
A patriot Carlisle first met on the battlefield at Yorktown
他将会成为我们最意外的同盟
would become our most unlikely ally.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
我痛恨英国的第一次入侵
I hated the first British Invasion.
但是第二次入侵更让人痛恨
And I hate the second one even more.
就连披头士乐队也讨厌?
Even the Beatles?
不是吧 加勒特?
Really, Garrett?
旧习难改啊
Old habits die hard.
卡莱尔需要你
Carlisle needs you.
似乎很有意思
Sounds interesting.
救命!
Help!
但是我要先把晚饭给吃了
But first I'd better finish my meal.
救命! 救命!
Help me! Help!
每一个人都被说服了
Each of them was won over.
每一个人都得以亲证
Each was made to see.
卡莱尔说服了他在爱尔兰的朋友到福克斯一游
Carlisle convinced his Irish friends to make the journey to Forks.
尽管我们很感激他们的帮忙
Although we were grateful for their help,
但是他们对人血的渴求 使得情况复杂化
their thirst for human blood complicated the situation.
而罗莎莉和埃米特带来的游牧民 更是深不可测
The nomads Rosalie and Emmett sent were even more unpredictable.
尤其是彼得
Especially Peter
自成为新生吸血鬼之时 就一直与贾斯珀打斗
who had fought alongside Jasper as a newborn.
到处都是血红的眼睛
Lotta red eyes around here.
他们同意不在这一区域猎食
They agreed not to hunt in the area.
但他们会在其他地方吸血
But they'll feed somewhere.
随着越来越多的吸血鬼踏足到他们的领地
As more vampires set foot in their territory,
越来越多的奎尔尤特族人开始变身
more Quileutes turned.
他们的天性 迫使他们加入狼群
Their nature compelling them to join the pack.
嘿 别激动 嘿!
Hey, easy there. Hey!
没事的
It's all right.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
最后 卡莱尔和爱斯梅与我们最后一名证人 一同归来
Finally, Carlisle and Esme returned with our last witness.
- 来了多少人?  - 十八个
- How many came?  - Eighteen.
你确实有些好朋友
You have some good friends.
爱丽丝有消息吗?
And Alice?
我们现在都成了阿罗的目标
We'll all be on Aro's list now.
逃了几个世纪 你们给我招惹了这种事
Centuries on the run. That's what you've brought me.
这就是所谓的朋友 卡莱尔
Some friend, Carlisle.
亚力斯泰尔 来跟大家打个招呼
Alistair, come meet everyone.
我已经跟你说过 如果要战斗 我是不会和沃尔图里作对的
I already told you, if it comes to a fight, I won't stand against the Volturi.
不会打起来的
It won't come to a fight.
我去阁楼呆着吧
I'll be in the attic.
他习惯独来独往
He's not a people person.
我们家迎来了十八个吸血鬼
We opened our home to 18 vampires.
他们各有各的能力
Many with gifts of their own.
扎弗里娜拥有影响思维的能力
Zafrina had power over the mind.
能让你看到任何她想要你看的东西
She could make anyone see what she wanted them to.
如果不是她握着我的手 我会以为眼前这些是真的
If she weren't holding my hand right now, I could swear this was real.
我什么也看不见
I don't see anything.
爱德华 你没有告诉我 你的妻子是防护盾
Edward, you didn't tell me your wife is a shield.
什么是防护盾?
What's a shield?
你不同于我认识的那些人
The ones I've met are so different.
这是一种防御性的能力
It's a defensive talent.
所以我无法读到你的思维 即使是在从前
It's why I couldn't read your mind, even before.
而阿罗也无法看穿
It's why Aro couldn't.
你拥有非常强大的能力
You have a very powerful gift.
哦 好吧 她是防护盾
Oh, yeah, she's a shield, all right.
还想着给她吃点苦头
Shoulda put her on her ass.
或者是你的电力其实没那么厉害
Or your voltage has been exaggerated.
也许它只在弱者身上起效
Maybe it only works on the weak.
加勒特 别惹她
Garrett, I wouldn't.
你真是个了不起的女人
You are an amazing woman.
你们现在的破坏力极强
Now, you guys can do some serious damage.
所以你们必须控制自己的变身
Which is why you'll need to control your phasing.
你可不想在一怒之下 就扯掉了自己妈妈的脑袋
If your mom pisses you off, you don't want to tear her head off.
不管来者是何人 都并未受到邀请
Whoever's coming wasn't invited.
呜呼!
Whoopa!
是弗拉基米尔和斯特凡
Vladimir, Stefan,
你们离家千里啊
you're a long way from home.
他们来这里干嘛?
What are they doing here?
我们听说沃尔图里一族 正前来对付你们
We heard the Volturi were moving against you.
但是你们并不是人单势孤
But that you would not stand alone.
我们并没有犯下那些罪行
We didn't do what we were accused of.
卡莱尔 我们不在乎你们做了什么
We do not care what you did, Carlisle.
我们已经等了一千年
We have been waiting a millennium
等着这群意大利败类被人挑战
for the Italian scum to be challenged.
我们并不打算与沃尔图里对决
It's not our plan to fight the Volturi.
真可惜
Shame.
阿罗的证人将会非常失望
Aro's witnesses will be so disappointed.
他们很喜欢激烈的打斗
They enjoy a good fight.
阿罗的证人?
Aro's witnesses?
哦
Aww.
还期盼着他们会听你们的解释?
Still hoping they'll listen?
但阿罗看中了其他家族的某个人之时
When Aro wants someone from a coven
用不了多久 就能找到证据去证明这个家庭确实有罪
it's never long before evidence turns up proving that coven committed some crime.
他以前就做过这种事?
So he's done this before?
很少 我都没意识到这是一种惯例了
It happens so rarely, I never realized it was a pattern.
显然他总会宽恕那些被他称为有悔改之心的人
Apparently he always pardons one person whose thoughts he claims are repentant.
但这种人 通常都具备特殊能力
This person always has an ability.
他们会在护卫队中占有一席之地
And they're always given a place with the Guard.
这是冲着爱丽丝来的
This is all about Alice.
- 他那里没有人拥有她的这种能力  - 所以她才离开
- He has no one like her.  - Which is why she left.
那他为什么需要证人呢?
Why does he need witnesses?
就是为了散播正义得到伸张的消息
To spread the word that justice has been served.
在他屠杀了整个族系之后
After he slaughters an entire coven.
本杰明 蒂亚
Benjamin, Tia,
- 我们走吧  - 你们能去哪里?
- we're leaving.  - And where will you go?
你凭什么认为 他们得到爱丽丝之后就会满足?
What makes you think they'll be satisfied with Alice?
难保本杰明就是他们下一个要抓的对象
What's to stop them from going after Benjamin next?
又或者是扎弗里娜 或是凯特
Or Zafrina or Kate
或是其他有才能的人? 只要是被他们看中
or anyone else with a gift? Anyone they want.
他们的目的并不在于惩戒 而是能力
Their goal isn't punishment, it's power.
是为了获取
It's acquisition.
卡莱尔也许不会请求你们加入战斗 但我会
Carlisle might not ask you to fight, but I will.
为了我家人的安危 但也是为了你们自己
For the sake of my family. But also for yours.
为了你们想要的生活方式而战
And for the way you want to live.
狼族愿意加入战斗
The packs will fight.
我们从不害怕吸血鬼
We've never been afraid of vampires.
我们会加入战斗
We will fight.
这也不是我第一次对抗国王的统治了
This won't be the first time I fought a king's rule.
我们会加入你们
We'll join you.
不
No.
阿蒙 我要做正确的事情
I will do the right thing, Amun.
你也可以做你自己想做的
You may do as you please.
我们会与你们并肩作战
We will stand with you.
我们也会
So will we.
人不也多嘛
That didn't take much.
但愿不会开战
Let's hope it doesn't come to that.
等着瞧吧
We'll see.
每个人都表现出勇气
Everyone showed courage.
尽管我们知道 阿罗的大军正朝我们赶来
Though we knew that Aro's army was moving against us.
很快 我们就要面对简的黑暗力量
Soon we would face the dark gifts of Jane.
更可怕的是 她的弟弟释放出来的麻痹气体
And worse, the paralyzing vapor of her brother Alec
会让人失去视觉 听觉 以及触觉
who could rob you of sight, sound and touch.
我拒绝了他!
I refused him!
我不会支持卡莱尔的!
I'm not with Carlisle!
亚历克?
Alec?
我绝不会与你作对
I will never go against you.
当然不会
Of course not,
亲爱的敏郎
my dear Toshiro.
似乎卡莱尔仍在等着你
It seems Carlisle is still expecting you.
卡莱尔现在也是自身难保
Carlisle is all but ensuring his own destruction.
真可怜
Sad,
对吧?
isn't it?
在阿罗进攻之前 他会希望夺去我们的作战能力
Aro will want us incapacitated before he attacks.
而简和亚历克会想办法先把我弄出去 因为我能看透他们的行动
Jane and Alec will try and take me out first because I can anticipate their moves.
可惜我们没有你那种防护能力
Too bad we don't all have your shield.
但这对我的战斗并无帮助
Doesn't help me fight, though.
不 你可以帮我们大家
No, but you could help the rest of us,
如果你能够放射出防护能力
if you could project it.
此话怎讲?
What do you mean?
除了防护你自己 也防护其他人
I mean shield someone other than yourself.
可能吗?
Is that possible?
能力经过一段时间 是可以发展的
Gifts can be developed. Over time.
我的电力 一开始只存在于掌心之中
At first, mine was just in my palms.
而现在我可以把它辐射到全身
Now I can radiate it all over my body.
你是怎么做到的?
How do you do it?
- 告诉我  - 噢
- Tell me.  - Ow.
你必须对它进行设想
You need to visualize it.
看看它是如何移动的
See how it moves.
它是什么颜色的
What color it is.
现在 用意念想象着它在扩张
Now picture it expanding.
让它从你体内释放出来
Will it to go beyond you.
我觉得她需要一点动力
I think she needs something to motivate her.
- 不  - 没关系 我能承受
- No.  - It's all right, I can take it.
这可是他说的
He says that now.
贝拉 集中注意力 否则他会受伤的
Focus, Bella, or he's gonna be hurting.
爱德华 我还没有准备好去应对这情形
Edward, I'm not ready to do this yet.
对不起 我说了我还没有准备好
I'm sorry. I said that I wasn't ready.
老兄 你并没有给她动力啊
Dude, you're not motivating her.
你想要试一试吗?
You want to try?
凯特!
Kate!
你似乎缺乏刺激
You seem to lack incentive.
要我去看看蕾妮斯梅醒了吗?
Shall I go see if Renesmee's awake?
你疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
好吧
All right.
这一次是贯注了全部力量
This one's on full power.
有点痛 但是可以承受
It's painful, but it's bearable.
好的 我们应该再试试
Okay, we should go again.
埃米特 你来
Emmett.
我就算了吧
I'm good.
甜美音乐缓缓而来
"There's sweet music here that"
柔若玫瑰花瓣落入草丛
"softer falls than petals from blown roses on the grass."
涧边石墙水珠凝集
"Or night dews on still waters between walls"
夜露微光轻闪
"of shadowy granite in a gleaming pass."
阵阵天籁 伴你进入甜蜜梦乡
"Music that brings sweet sleep down from the blissful skies."
妈
Mom.
嗯?
Hmm?
爱丽丝姑姑和贾斯珀叔叔离开
Did Aunt Alice and Uncle Jasper run away
是因为我们快要死了吗?
because we're gonna die?
不
No.
我想他们离开 是为了让我们更加安全
I think they left to keep us safer.
其他人也是因为这个原因 而聚在这里
That's what all these other people are here for, too.
我绝不会让任何人伤害你
I'll never let anybody hurt you.
来 安心睡吧
Come here. Go to sleep.
感觉真奇怪
It's strange.
我觉得自己体力充沛 足以摧毁一辆坦克
Physically, I feel like I could demolish a tank.
可是精神上却觉得非常疲累
Mentally, I just feel drained.
要不去泡个澡吧?
How about a bath?
我还记得怎样给自己脱衣服
I do remember how to undress myself.
是嘛 可是我脱得比你更快
Yeah, I just do it so much better.
贝拉
Bella,
我总是习惯性地去低估你
I've had a bad habit of underestimating you.
每次你碰到阻碍
Every obstacle you've faced,
我都会以为你无法克服
I'd think you couldn't overcome it.
而你却克服了
And you just did.
是给你给了他们奋战的理由
You're the reason they have something to fight for.
我的家人
My family.
我先去放水
I'm gonna get the water running.
(J·詹克斯 西雅图 看后即毁)
爱丽丝确保只有我能够看到这个信息
Alice made sure only I would get the message.
因为只有我的想法 是阿罗无法读到的
Because only my mind would be safe from Aro.
你居然愿意暂停魔鬼训练 真让我意外
I'm surprised you took a break from Jedi training.
如果我不把蕾妮斯梅带去我爸家 他会来找我们的
If I don't take Renesmee to my dad, he'll come to us.
那里有27个吸血鬼 1个人类
27 vampires, one human.
这样不太好
Not so great.
我知道这是你对爱德华的说辞
I know that's what you told Edward.
随你吧
Whatever.
我只是很高兴能够远离那些臭死人的吸血鬼
I'm just glad to get away from all those reeking bloodsuckers.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我懂的
I know.
他们都是好人
They're the good guys.
但是拜托
But come on,
吸血鬼德拉库拉一代和二代
Dracula One and Two are
都很惊悚
creepy.
她到了 过来
There she is. Come here.
噢!
Oh!
哇! 瞧瞧你
Wow! Look at you.
你又长高了半英尺
You've grown half a foot!
说真的
Seriously.
长高了六英寸
Like 6 inches.
进来吧 午饭做好了
Come on inside. Lunch is on the table.
我们还有圣诞树要装饰呢
We got a tree to decorate, huh?
其实我还有些事情要办
I've actually got a few errands to run, guys.
我马上回来 好吗?
I'll be back soon, okay?
来吧 我们进去
Come on. Let's go.
爱丽丝的便笺 带给我新的希望
Alice's note gave me a new sense of hope.
也许她最后还是能够帮我们想出办法
Maybe she had a plan for us after all.
也许这个J·詹克斯就是关键
And maybe J. Jenks was the key.
- 我是来找詹克斯先生的  - 请跟我来
- I'm meeting Mr. Jenks.  - Right this way.
- 柯伦太太  - 你好
- Mrs. Cullen.  - Hi.
很高兴你能够来电
I'm so happy you called.
我总是在这里与我的私人客户会面
I always meet my private clients here.
这里比办公室更自在
It's more comfortable than the office.
而且更为大庭广众
And it's more public.
啊
Ah.
请问你是做什么工作的?
What type of work do you do, J.?
哦 就是一些琐事
Oh, you know, this and that.
各不相同 所以很有意思
It's always different, which keeps it interesting.
你认识爱丽丝和贾斯珀很久了?
Have you known Alice and Jasper long?
我已经为他们服务了二十多年
I've been working with them for more than 20 years.
我已故的搭档 在此之前已经认识贾斯珀十五年了
And my late partner knew Jasper 15 years before that.
他嘛
He is, uh,
保养得非常好
unusually well-preserved.
确实如此
Yes, he is.
我相信贾斯珀先生很享受自己的假期
I trust that Mr. Jasper is enjoying his vacation.
他并没有告诉你他去了哪里 对吧?
He didn't tell you where he was going, did he?
没有 他过来下订单的时候
No, no, no, he just mentioned that he was leaving
只提到自己要离开
when he came by to place his order.
我想 他的订单已经准备好了吧?
I assume that his order is ready?
当然
Of course.
我送东西 从来都是很准时的
I've never been late with a delivery.
有问题吗?
There a problem?
没有
No.
只是我和我丈夫以为 我们大家会一起去旅行
My husband and I thought that we'd all be traveling together.
贾斯珀说出行的只有两位
Jasper said only two were traveling.
他的指示说得非常明白
His instructions were very clear.
是我弄错了
It's my mistake.
显然 这是不可能的
Apparently, that's not going to happen.
爱丽丝预见得非常清楚
Alice's vision was clear.
蕾妮斯梅会有未来
Renesmee would have a future.
但我和爱德华并没有参与在内
But Edward and I wouldn't be a part of it.
你还好吗?
How ya doing?
我最亲爱的蕾妮斯梅
"My dearest Renesmee,"
我原以为 我们可以永远在一起
"I thought we would have forever together."
但是这个永远 并不如我所希望的那么长久
"But forever isn't as long as I'd hoped."
我现在知道 爱丽丝为何给我留下线索
"I know now why Alice left me clues."
这是为了保你周全
"It was to keep you safe."
你和雅各布只需要待在狼族里
"Everything you and Jacob will need is in this pack."
雅各布会保护你
"Jacob will protect you."
他还会帮你了解到图库纳的传说
"And he'll help you learn about the Ticuna legends."
这是种浪漫的想法 对吧?
It's a romantic notion, isn't it?
认为正义能够以少数 战胜邪恶的多数
That a righteous few can defy a great evil.
我必须肯定 你让我相信了这一点
I must admit, you even had me believing.
就那么片刻
For a moment.
祝你好运 你会需要用到这个的
Well, good luck. You're gonna need it.
加油
Cheers.
开始积雪了
The snow is sticking.
嘿 我们仍拥有今日
Hey, we still have today.
我很高兴查理身边有人能够照顾他
I'm so glad Charlie found somebody to take care of him.
贝拉 大家都没有放弃
Bella, no one's giving up here.
好了! 派礼物啦! 开始了
All right! Present time! Let's go!
塞斯 莉亚 不要吃了
Seth, Leah, stop eating.
雅各布 你先开始 赶紧的
Jake, you start. Get it going.
- 你给我准备了什么礼物?  - 我什么也不打算算
- What did you get me?  - I'm not giving you anything.
嘿! 别这样 你给我准备了什么呀?
Hey! No, come on, what did you get me?
爸 我们没有时间包装礼物
Well, Dad, we didn't have time to wrap yours,
这是送你的
but here it is.
是弗雷泽河的五日垂钓航行
It's a 5-day fishing trip to Fraser River.
是送给你和苏的
It's for you and Sue.
你们明天早上就出发
You leave tomorrow.
哇 真棒 谢谢
Wow, that's really nice. Thank you.
明天? 我明天可不能走
Tomorrow? I can't leave tomorrow.
我已经帮你把工作安排好了
I made arrangements for you at work.
你们背着我
Sneaky.
而且非常奢侈
And extravagant.
恐怕这个是不能退钱的
And non-refundable, I'm afraid.
你们俩是想要甩掉我吗?
You two trying to get rid of me?
因为你们确实如愿了!
Because it's working!
弗雷泽河 这么说我们可以去追踪海盗
Fraser River. That means we'll be chasing Cutthroat.
我们还可能钓到虹鳟鱼或是公海豹
We might even hook a Rainbow or some Bulls.
女人还真是容易知足
Woman knows her trout.
嘿 真漂亮 让我看看
Hey, beautiful. Let me see.
是雅各布给你做的吗?
Jacob make this for you?
想要戴上吗?
Wanna put it on?
很好看
It's so pretty.
真的很好看
It is really pretty.
我就是想要这个
That's what I'm talkin' about.
战前的篝火之夜
A little pre-battle bonfire.
讲一些战争的故事
Telling war stories.
又或者是光站在那边 像是一些怪异的雕塑
Or just standing there like freackin' statues.
随便说哪个美国的战役 我都参与了
Name any American battle. I was there.
小巨角战役
Little Bighorn.
我差一点就咬住了卡斯特将军
I came this close to biting Custer.
但是他被印第安人先抓获了
But the Indians got him first.
奥列格攻打君士坦丁堡时
Try Oleg's assault on Constantinople.
他并不是靠自己打胜仗的
He didn't win that one on his own.
要说战争
If you're talking battles,
那就必须说到十一年战争
you're talking the Eleven Years' War.
从未有人像爱尔兰人那样叛乱
No one does rebellion like the Irish.
你们输掉了十一年战争
You lost the Eleven Years' War.
是啊 这场叛乱可真是可怕
Aye. But it was one hell of a rebellion.
当我们掌权之后 什么事都找上门
When we ruled, everything came to us.
受害者
Prey,
外交官
diplomats,
投机者
favor seekers.
尽管我们强大
Such was our power.
但我们从不给自己戴高帽 也不以圣人自居
But we never put on white hats and called ourselves saints.
我们不会对自己加以掩饰
We were honest about what we were.
我们静坐了好长一段时间
We sat still for a very long time.
竟未察觉自己已经开始石化
We didn't notice we were beginning to petrify.
直到沃尔图里家族把我们的城堡烧掉
Perhaps the Volturi did us a favor when they
或许还得感谢他们
burned our castles.
我们已经等了一千五百年
We've been waiting 1,500 years
就为了报这个仇
to return that favor.
几个世纪以来 我们枕戈待旦
We have been ready to do battle for ages.
我不禁去想
I can't help thinking,
这些人身处险境
all these people are putting themselves in danger
只因我爱上了人类
because I fell in love with a human.
你找到了自己的另一半
You found your mate.
你应该幸福
You deserve to be happy.
但是要付出什么代价?
But at what cost?
每个人都有自己奋战的理由
Everyone here has something to fight for.
我当然也有
I certainly do.
卡莱尔 我从未感谢过你
Carlisle, I've never thanked you.
给予我这非凡的人生
For this extraordinary life.
这代表"比自己的生命更甚"
This means "More than my own life."
我是如此地爱你
That's how much I love you.
我要你明天和雅各布待在一起
Tomorrow I'm gonna need you to stay with Jacob.
无论发生什么事
No matter what.
哪怕是我叫他...
Even if I tell him that...
把你带离这里
That he has to take you somewhere.
嘿
Hey.
宝贝 没事的
Baby, it's all right.
你会平平安安的
You're gonna be safe.
一直都会
Always.
如果这次我们能够活下来
If we live through this,
我愿意追随你到天涯海角 女人
I'll follow you anywhere, woman.
你总算开口了
Now you tell me.
红衫军来了! 红衫军来了!
The Redcoats are coming! The Redcoats are coming!
阿罗正在找爱丽丝
Aro's looking for Alice.
阿罗
Aro,
让我们像以往那样 和平议事
let us discuss things as we used to.
以文明的方式
In a civilized manner.
说得倒是好听 卡莱尔
Fair words, Carlisle.
但似乎不合时宜
But a little out of place,
因为你集聚了大军来与我们对抗
given the battalion you've assembled against us.
我保证 这并非是我的本意
I can promise you, that was never my intent.
我们并没有违法
No laws have been broken.
我们看到了那个孩子
We see the child.
别以为我们是傻瓜
Do not treat us as fools.
她不是吸血鬼!
She is not an Immortal!
这些证人能够作证
These witnesses can attest to that.
或者你亲眼瞧瞧
Or you can look.
瞧她双颊上的血色
See the flush of human blood in her cheeks.
诡计!
Artifice!
我会收集各方面的真相
I will collect every facet of the truth.
但作为案件里更关键的人物
But from someone more central to the story.
爱德华
Edward,
既然这个孩子与你的吸血鬼伴侣有关系
as the child clings to your newborn mate,
我猜 你也牵涉在内
I assume you are involved.
我想要见一见她
I'd like to meet her.
啊
Ah.
年轻的贝拉
Young Bella.
你变得长生不老了
Immortality becomes you.
我听到她奇特的心跳声
I hear her strange heart.
你好 阿罗
Hello, Aro.
真让人惊讶!
Magnifico!
一半是凡人
Half mortal,
一半是不朽之人
half immortal.
都被这个新生儿
Conceived and carried by this
集于一身
newborn
当她仍是人类之时
while she was still human.
不可能!
Impossible!
你认为他们是在骗我吗 弟弟?
Do you think they fooled me, brother?
把告发者带上来
Bring the informer forward.
你看到的就是这个孩子吗?
Is that the child you saw?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
简
Jane.
她有些变化 这孩子长得更大一些
She's changed. This child is bigger.
那么你的指控是错的
Then your allegations were false.
柯伦一家是无辜的
The Cullens are innocent.
我会为自己的错 承担全部责任
I take full responsibility for my mistake.
对不起
I'm sorry.
凯厄斯 不要!
Caius, no!
伊丽娜!
Irina!
让他们失明
Blind them.
把视觉还给我
Give me my sight back.
塔尼娅 这正好着了他们的道
Tanya, this is what they want.
如果你现在发起攻击 我们大家都会死
If you attack now, we'll all die.
痛
Pain.
起作用了
It's working.
阿罗 我们并没有违法
Aro, you see there's no law broken here.
赞同
Agreed.
但这是否意味着
But does it then follow
这并不具有危险性呢?
that there is no danger?
这是我们史上首次
For the first time in our history
由人类对我们
humans pose a threat
产生了威胁
to our kind.
他们的现代技术
Their modern technology
制造出可以摧毁我们的工具
has given birth to weapons that could destroy us.
使得保守我们的秘密
Maintaining our secret
变得更加迫在眉睫
has never been more imperative.
在这种危险的时刻
In such perilous times,
只有已知的事物
only the known
才是安全的
is safe.
只有已知的事物
Only the known
才是可接受的
is tolerable.
而我们并不知道
And we know nothing
这个孩子会变成什么
of what this child will become.
我们能够承受这种不确实性吗?
Can we live with such uncertainty?
今日我们免于一战
Spare ourselves a fight today,
只能换来
only to die
明日之死
tomorrow.
不
No.
爱丽丝
Alice.
爱丽丝!
Alice!
我亲爱的爱丽丝
My dear, dear Alice,
很高兴终于见到你出现了
we're so glad to see you here, after all.
我有证据证明这个孩子不会威胁到我们这一族群
I have evidence the child won't be a risk to our kind.
让我展示给你看
Let me show you.
弟弟?
Brother?
你并不会在乎我给你看了些什么
It doesn't matter what I show you.
哪怕你确实看到
Even when you see.
你都不会改变你的决定
You still won't change your decision.
赶紧!
Now!
照顾好我的女儿
Take care of my daughter.
抓住他们
Get them.
哼!
Hmm!
带她走
Take her away.
放开她!
Let her go!
雅各布!
Jacob!
小心!
Watch out!
贝拉!
Bella!
终于到我了
Finally.
现在你知道了
Now you know.
这就是你的未来
That's your future.
除非你改变决定
Unless you decide on another course.
我们不能改变决定 这孩子仍是极大的威胁
We cannot alter our course. The child still poses a grave threat.
但是如果你们能够确定
But what if you were sure she could
她不会在人类的世界里暴露身份呢?
remain concealed from the human world?
我们能够和平相处吗?
Could we leave in peace?
当然可以 但是我们怎能确定
Of course. But that cannot be known.
实际上 可以确定
Actually, it can.
我一直在巴西的图库纳部落中
I've been searching for witnesses of my own
寻找我自己的证人
among the Ticuna tribes of Brazil.
- 我们也有足够的证人  - 听他说 弟弟
- We have enough witnesses.  - Let him speak, brother.
我是半人类
I am half human,
半吸血鬼
half vampire.
像那个孩子一样
Like the Child.
我妈妈被吸血鬼给引诱了
A vampire seduced my mother,
然后在生我的时候死去
who died giving birth to me.
是我的阿姨休伊伦
My aunt Huilen
亲自把我抚养成人
raised me as her own.
我把她变成吸血鬼
I made her immortal.
你现在多少岁了?
How old are you?
150岁
150 years.
你是在几岁的时候长大成人?
At what age did you reach maturity?
在我出生后的第七年 我就已经发育完全
I became full-grown seven years after my birth.
然后我就再也没有改变过
I have not changed since then.
那你都吃些什么?
And your diet?
血
Blood,
人类的食物
human food.
这两样食物都可以养活我
I can survive on either.
这些孩子和我们很像
These children are much like us.
但是柯伦一家与狼人为伍
Regardless, the Cullens have been consorting with werewolves.
这是我们的天敌
Our natural enemies.
亲爱的
Dear ones,
这里很安全
there is no danger here.
我们不会开战
We will not fight
就今天而言
today.
奖品真诱人
Such a prize.
他们在逃跑 是时候发起攻击了
We have them on the run. Now is the time to attack.
今天不行
Not today.
你们这群笨蛋!
You're all fools!
沃尔图里家族或许离开了
The Volturi might be gone.
但他们绝对不会原谅
But they will never forgive
这里发生的事
what happened here.
你拥有一个美好的家庭
You have a beautiful family.
她会陪着我们好久 对吧?
She's gonna be around for a long time, isn't she?
很久很久
A very long time.
幸好有你陪着她
I'm glad she has you.
所以我应该开始叫你"爸爸"吗?
So should I start calling you "Dad"?
不要
No.
嘿
Hey.
是的 现在我们可以在一起了
Yeah. We're all gonna be together now.
我想给你看点东西
I wanna show you something.
什么?
What?
我是爱德华·柯伦
I'm Edward Cullen.
你是怎么做到的?
How did you do that?
练习了好久
Been practicing.
现在你知道了
Now you know.
不会有谁能像我这么地爱你
Nobody's ever loved anybody as much as I love you.
还有一个女人除外
There's one exception.
能再给我看看吗?
Will you show me again?
我们还有很多的时间
We've got a lotta time.
永远
Forever.